A Guide to the Barksdale Theatre Records 1945-2006 (bulk 1954-2004)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Barksdale Theatre Records 1945-2006 (bulk 1954-2004)
Library of Virginia
41088
48.06 cubic feet; 109 boxes and 1 oversized drawer; Box numbers 1-109.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Barksdale Theatre, Richmond, Virginia, 8 January 2004. Two broadsides were interfiled with the collection, Accession 41248. Gift of Jacquie O'Connor, Richmond, Virginia, 14 June 2004. Several programs were interfiled with the colleciton, Accession 42150. Transferred from Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Richmond, Virginia, 26 August 2005.
Biographical/Historical Information
Barksdale Theatre was created by a group of friends who met during summer stock theatre in St. Clair, Michigan. The original founders were Tom Carlin, Stewart Falconer, David and Priscilla Kilgore, Muriel McAuley, and Pat Sharp. In June 1953 they moved to Richmond, Virginia, desiring to start their own theatre. The group purchased the historic Hanover Tavern in Hanover, Virginia, 1 August 1953, and established the nation's first dinner theatre, Barksdale Memorial Theatre. The theatre was named in memory of a deceased college friend, Barbara Barksdale (1930-1950). The theatre produced their first play, Gold in the Hills, at Barksdale Theatre, on 23 September 1954.
By 1960, four of the original members had left Barksdale, and David Kilgore had married Nancy Masters. The three remaining members, David and Nancy Kilgore, and Muriel McAuley lead the theatre for the next 40 years. Throughout those years they produced over 200 plays and renovated Hanover Tavern. In 1973, Barksdale produced the first professional production of a play based on African American experience, Lorraine Hansberry's To Be Young, Gifted, and Black. In 1975, they staged the first professional reenactment of Patrick Henry's "Liberty or Death" speech at the historic St. John's Church. In 1977 Barksdale produced the world premiere of Red, Hot, and Cole, an original play written by Muriel McAuley and Randy Strawderman. After hundreds of performances and the raising of several children and animals, in 1990 the founding members sold Hanover Tavern to the Hanover Tavern Foundation. The founders retired in 1993, naming John Glenn as artistic director. Of the founding members, Nancy Kilgore died 16 October 1993, and Muriel McAuley died 4 September 1998.
In 1996 Barksdale built and moved into a new facility at Willow Lawn Shopping Center in Richmond, Virginia. Randy Strawderman served as artistic director from 1997-2001. Currently, 2004, Bruce Miller serves as artistic director of Barksdale Theatre which continues the tradition of producing excellent theatre. For additional history of the theatre please consult, Going On...Barksdale Theatre The First Thirty One Years by Muriel McAuley (Taylor Publishing Co., 1984).
Scope and Content
The Barksdale Records are housed in 109 boxes and one oversized drawer. Included are bylaws, contracts, correspondence, deeds, financial materials, ledgers, minutes, musical scores, newsletters, newspaper clippings, photographs, posters, press releases, programs, receipts, reports, resumes, scrapbooks, and scripts. The records document the development of the company from its earliest performances at Hanover Tavern, to its contemporary performances at the Willow Lawn Center.
The records include deeds for Hanover Tavern and Willow Lawn Center, correspondence regarding literary rights of plays, scripts submitted by inspiring playwrights, fundraising campaign materials, articles of incorporation, Board of Trustee minute files, and personnel policy manuals. Although the collection includes records relating to the financial and managerial side of the business, they are sparse and incomplete.
The bulk of the collection are the clippings, photographs, posters, production files, programs, and reviews documenting the over 200 productions performed by the theatre in its 50 year history. Included are hundreds of photographs from the earliest productions to the current season, numerous theater programs, production files including directing books, cast contact lists, rehearsal schedules, and scripts, theater critic newspaper reviews, and posters of the productions. The collection also includes videos of some of the original performances. Two appendixes are available at the end of the finding aid listing all of the productions performed at Barksdale. One appendix is arranged chronologically, one alphabetically, and they record whether photographs or programs are available for the production. These appendixes are not available online.
A more in-depth description of the collection can be found in the Series level description. It is recommended that the researcher read the Series level scope and content notes thoroughly before accessing the collection.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Building Management Files, 1954-1996
Series II. Correspondence, General, 1955-2000
Series III. Correspondence and Scripts, Playwrights, 1979-1998
Series IV. Financial Records, 1953-2001
Series V. Newsclippings and Newsletters, 1953-2002
Series VI. Production Files, 1954-2000
Series VII. Programs, 1954-2004
Series VIII. Theatre Management Records, 1954-2001
Series IX. Miscellaenous, 1945-1998
Series X. Scrapbooks, 1950-2000
Series XI. Oversize, 1954-2003
Series XII. Photographs, 1954-1999
Series XIII. Audio-Visual Materials, 1966-1993
Series XIV. Artifacts/Ephemera, 1954-2000
Contents List
- Series I. Building Management Files, 1954-1996., Extent: .35 cu. ft. (1 box). (Box 1)
  The Building Management Papers Series is housed in 1 box and arranged alphabetically by folder title. The papers include architectural plans, contracts, deeds, incorporation charter, leases, and reports. Included are minutes and reports from the Hanover Tavern Foundation Building and Grounds committee meetings. Also included are brochures and newsletters regarding the efforts by the Hanover Tavern Foundation to preserve and restore Hanover Tavern, 1993-1996, and contracts, correspondence, and floor plans for the building of the Barksdale Theatre at Willow Lawn Center, 1996. Of note are the deeds between the Barksdale Theater and Hanover Tavern, 1954-1990, including the original deed for Hanover Tavern dated 1 August 1953.
  Oversized architectural plans can be found in Oversize Series XI, Subseries 5: Miscellaneous. They include drawings of Hanover Tavern by the Historic American Building Survey, 1990.
  - Barksdale Theatre Building Task Force 1995 (Box-folder 1:1)
  - Cocktail list n.d. (Box-folder 1:2)
  - Contracts 1974-1996 (Box-folder 1:3)
  - Deeds 1954-1990 (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Hanover Tavern Foundation, Buildings and Grounds Committee 1993-1996 (Box-folder 1:5)
    See Oversize Subseries 5 for Hanover Tavern Project drawings and specifications, 1992, by Historic American Building Survey, and Correspondence and sketches from Hanson Associates, 1990. Includes sketch of Hanover Tavern parking area; basement floor
  - Hanover Tavern Foundation, Preservation campaigns 1993-1996 (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Incorporation charter 1973 (Box-folder 1:7)
  - Leases 1990-1996 (Box-folder 1:8)
  - Willow Lawn (Richmond, VA) construction 1996 (Box-folder 1:9)
- Series II. Correspondence, General, 1955-2000., Extent: .70 cu. ft. (2 boxes). (Box 2-3)
  The General Correspondence Series is housed in 2 boxes and arranged chronologically. The correspondence documents the many aspects of managing Barksdale Theatre, encompassing fund raising, literary rights and royalties, maintenance issues, and exchanges with critics, subscribers and audiences. Included are letters and memoranda regarding appeals for funds, invitations to critics, advertising issues, congratulatory letters, requests for tickets, and production rights. Also included are letters to various statesmen concerning issues such as minimum wages and taxation issues which affected the theatre. Early correspondence, 1954-1969, includes letters to and from Muriel McAuley and Priscilla Kilgore regarding production rights and royalty fees, mainly to the companies of Samuel French, Inc., and Dramatists Play Service, Inc.
  Also included is correspondence, 1995-1996, regarding the move of the Barksdale Theatre from Hanover Tavern, Hanover, to Willow Lawn Center in Richmond, Virginia. Topics include the search for another home for the theatre, lease and rental conditions between the two organizations, and financial costs for the move to Richmond. Many of the letters in the 1990's are to John Glenn and Randy Strawderman, Artistic Directors for the Barksdale Theatre.
  - Correspondence 1955 (Box-folder 2:1)
  - Correspondence (originals) 1955 (Box-folder 2:2)
  - Correspondence 1956 (Box-folder 2:3)
  - Correspondence (originals) 1956 (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Correspondence 1957 (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Correspondence (originals) 1957 (Box-folder 2:6)
  - Correspondence 1958 (Box-folder 2:7)
  - Correspondence (originals) 1958 (Box-folder 2:8)
  - Correspondence 1959 (Box-folder 2:9)
  - Correspondence 1960 (Box-folder 2:10)
  - Correspondence (originals) 1960 (Box-folder 2:11)
  - Correspondence 1961 (Box-folder 2:12)
  - Correspondence (originals) 1961 (Box-folder 2:13)
  - Correspondence 1962 (Box-folder 2:14)
  - Correspondence 1963 (Box-folder 2:15)
  - Correspondence (originals) 1963 (Box-folder 2:16)
  - Correspondence 1964-1969 (Box-folder 2:17)
  - Correspondence 1973-1979 (Box-folder 2:18)
  - Correspondence 1982-1988 (Box-folder 2:19)
  - Letters from Pat Carroll 1982-1990 (Box-folder 2:19a)
  - Correspondence 1990-1993 (Box-folder 2:20)
  - Correspondence 1994 January-June (Box-folder 2:21)
  - Correspondence 1994 July-December (Box-folder 3:1)
  - Correspondence 1995 (Box-folder 3:2)
  - Correspondence 1996 (Box-folder 3:3)
  - Correspondence 1997 (Box-folder 3:4)
  - Correspondence 1998 (Box-folder 3:5)
  - Correspondence 2000-2001 (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Correspondence Undated (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Cards 1983-2000 (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Cards 1983-2000 (Box-folder 3:9)
  - Envelopes, blank (Box-folder 3:10)
- Series III. Correspondence and scripts, Playwrights, 1979-1998., Extent: 3.5 cu. ft. (10 boxes). (Box 4-13)
  The Correspondence and Scripts, Playwrights, Series is housed in 10 boxes and arranged alphabetically by folder title. General correspondence is arranged to the front. Following the general correspondence are folders arranged alphabetically by playwright's last name. These playwrights have individual folders due to the larger size of the scripts submitted.
  Included are letters and either the entire play or a synopsis of a play. Often included were self addressed return envelopes and follow up letters. Some lyricists also included audio tapes of their music. The letters were from the authors or their agents, if they had one, and most letters were addressed to John Glenn or Randy Strawderman. The majority of the play submissions were made in the 1990's. Many of the letters were unopened when they were donated to the Library and were later opened by the archivist. Many of the writers sent in their plays after reading an advertisement by Barksdale in the Dramatists Sourcebook, asking for play submissions. Some authors include letters of recommendations, resumes, and reviews with their scripts.
  - General correspondence, A (Box-folder 4:1)
  - General correspondence, Ba-Bl (Box-folder 4:2)
  - General correspondence, Bo-Bu (Box-folder 4:3)
  - General correspondence, C (Box-folder 4:4)
  - General correspondence, D (Box-folder 4:5)
  - General correspondence, E-F (Box-folder 4:6)
  - General correspondence, Ga-Gi (Box-folder 5:1)
  - General correspondence, Go-Gr (Box-folder 5:2)
  - General correspondence, Ha (Box-folder 5:3)
  - General correspondence, He-Hl (Box-folder 5:4)
  - General correspondence, Ho-Hy (Box-folder 5:5)
  - General correspondence, I-Je (Box-folder 6:1)
  - General correspondence, Jo-Ju (Box-folder 6:2)
  - General correspondence, Ka-Ke (Box-folder 6:3)
  - General correspondence, Ko-Kr (Box-folder 6:4)
  - General correspondence, La-Le (Box-folder 6:5)
  - General correspondence, Li-Lu (Box-folder 6:6)
  - General correspondence, Ma-Mi (Box-folder 6:7)
  - General correspondence, Mo-Mu (Box-folder 6:8)
  - General correspondence, N (Box-folder 6:9)
  - General correspondence, O-P (Box-folder 7:1)
  - General correspondence, Ra-Re (Box-folder 7:2)
  - General correspondence, Ri-Ro (Box-folder 7:3)
  - General correspondence, Sa-Si (Box-folder 7:4)
  - General correspondence, Sm-Sw (Box-folder 7:5)
  - General correspondence, T-V (Box-folder 7:6)
  - General correspondence, W (Box-folder 7:7)
  - General correspondence, Y-Z (Box-folder 7:8)
  - General correspondence, Unknown (Box-folder 7:9)
  - Atterbury, Malcolm, The Art of Seduction (Box-folder 8:1)
  - Beardsley, Elaine, Sacagawea (Box-folder 8:2)
  - Black, Bill, Miss me yet? (Box-folder 8:3)
  - Black, Eugene, Camelot Lost, Immortal Beloved, and The Cleansing of George Cuthbert (Box-folder 8:4)
  - Blake, Evan, True Magic (Box-folder 8:5)
  - Brochu, Jim, The Lucky O'Learys (Box-folder 8:6)
  - Burch, Steve, The Bridge (audio tape included) (Box-folder 8:7)
  - Chalcraft, Roy, Executive Leverage (Box-folder 8:8)
  - Citron, Kirk, Acts of Violence (Box-folder 8:9)
  - Cooper, Leonard, The hypnotist (Box-folder 8:10)
  - Cowley, Joseph, I love you, I love you (Box-folder 8:11)
  - Dicintio, Matt, Nighthawks (Box-folder 8:12)
  - Dobson, Mary Lynn, Dracula, The Untold Story (Box-folder 8:13)
  - Doherty, Felix, Down the Nights (Box-folder 8:14)
  - Drake, Donald, Saintly Mother (Box-folder 9:1)
  - Finlayson, Alex, The Misfits (Box-folder 9:2)
  - Folb, Jay, A Mother's Death Wish (Box-folder 9:3)
  - Freek, George, Tortured Souls (Box-folder 9:4)
  - Geller, Arthur, Hotel Antoine, NY: 1941 (audio tape included) (Box-folder 9:5)
  - Giersch, Richard, And early through the Laurel grows (Box-folder 9:6)
  - Goode, Jeff, The Eight (Box-folder 9:7)
  - Griffin, Roger, The Piper (Box-folder 9:7a)
  - Hager, Eric, The Mailman's Kiss (Box-folder 9:8)
  - Hanley, Gene, Time Will Tell (Box-folder 9:9)
  - The death and sale of Alexander Goland (Box-folder 9:10)
  - Hite, Barbara, Sissy and the Baby Jesus (Box-folder 9:11)
  - Hoffman, Burton R., Tales of Hoffman (Box-folder 9:12)
  - Holmes, Philip W., A Good Drowning (Box-folder 10:1)
  - Hooper, Wilf, Hide and Sex (Box-folder 10:2)
  - Humphreys, Martha, Just Desserts (Box-folder 10:3)
  - Humphreys, Martha, Off the Walltons (Box-folder 10:4)
  - Iddings, Paul C., Tomatoes and Beer (Box-folder 10:5)
  - Kaasik, John, Murder by Mistake (Box-folder 10:6)
  - Kahn, James T., The Loophole (Box-folder 10:7)
  - Lapine, James, Sunday in the Park with George (Box-folder 10:8)
  - Lowenstein, Larry (Box-folder 10:9)
  - MacNicholas, John, Deja vu (Box-folder 10:10)
  - Mallatratt, Stephen, The Woman in Black (Box-folder 10:11)
  - Marguiles, Donald, Sight Unseen (Box-folder 11:1)
  - Marks, Jason, Looking for Canterbury (audio tape included) (Box-folder 11:2)
  - Mattia, Rita, Kenneth One, Two, Three (Box-folder 11:3)
  - McAuley, Muriel, Idea for television series (Box-folder 11:4)
  - Metcalfe, Steve, Strange Snow (Box-folder 11:4a)
  - Miller, Kenneth, Mothers (Box-folder 11:5)
  - Murphy, Gerald, Northwest Side Story (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Nhuong, Huynh Q., Neighing of a Stallion (Box-folder 11:7)
  - O'Keefe, Tara, Spider webs and Butterflies (Box-folder 11:8)
  - Olive, John, The Voice of the Prarie (Box-folder 11:9)
  - Pachino, Jamie, Race (Box-folder 11:10)
  - Packard, Steven, The Saturday Shoes, Four Hearts, and At the end of the rope (Box-folder 11:11)
  - Pailet, L., Toby Garson, and Janet Gari, Rapunzel of Riverside Drive (Box-folder 11:12)
  - Parr, Larry, Hi-Hat Hattie (Box-folder 11:13)
  - Post, Perrin, Ten Years Later (Box-folder 11:14)
  - Reed, Katherine, Shady Manor (Box-folder 11:14a)
  - Riccardi, Vince, Running Fox (Box-folder 11:15)
  - Rowe, T. Kenneth, Love at any age (Box-folder 12:1)
  - Sala, Edward, Two Brothers (Box-folder 12:2)
  - Samuels, Diane, Kindertransport (Box-folder 12:3)
  - Sartin, Laddy, Blessed Assurance (Box-folder 12:4)
  - Sessions, Robert P., Remind me to tell you (Box-folder 12:5)
  - Sibbald, George, Brothers (Box-folder 12:6)
  - Simon, Neil, Proposals (Box-folder 12:7)
  - Skinner, Jill E., The Forest Dream (audio tape included) (Box-folder 12:8)
  - Sleser, Henry, He had a hat (Box-folder 12:9)
  - Smith, Glenn, Curious in LA (Box-folder 12:10)
  - Smith, Glenn, Years in the Making (Box-folder 12:11)
  - Stronach, Cary E., For every great fortune (Box-folder 13:1)
  - Thomas, Charles P., Daylight Spirits (audio tape included) (Box-folder 13:2)
  - Waddington, Rona, Earhart (Box-folder 13:3)
  - Wagner, Helene, The Unseen (Box-folder 13:4)
  - Weeden, Bill, David Finkle, and Sally Fay, Move it and it's yours (Box-folder 13:5)
  - Wilson, Bo, The Caretaker (Box-folder 13:5a)
  - Wilson, Bo, Listen Close (Box-folder 13:6)
  - Wilson, Bo, War Stories (Box-folder 13:7)
  - Unknown, The Misfits (Box-folder 13:8)
  - Unknown (Box-folder 13:9)
- Series IV. Financial records, 1953-2001., Extent: 1.4 cu. ft. (4 boxes). (Box 14-17)
  The Financial Records Series is housed in 4 boxes and arranged alphabetically by folder title. This series includes correspondence, financial statements, fundraising campaign materials, grants, ledgers, and receipts. One of the earliest financial documents is the expense ledger, 1953 February-October, which includes accounts of monies spent on groceries, paint, cleaning supplies, gasoline, and medical bills. Of note are the financial statements, 1976-2000, which include balance sheets, statements of revenues and expenses, yearly budgets, income statement, accounts payable, payroll expense, and ticket sales reports. Included are budgets for individual shows containing expense summaries and ticket sales totals. The financial statements are the most complete for 1994-1996.
  Included are fundraising campaign papers, 1996-2001, which contain information on pledges, types of campaigns and program outlines, proposals, sponsorship letters, and advertisements. Also included are applications for grants from the Virginia Commission for the Arts and the Virginia Foundation for the Humanities and Public Policy.
  - Accounts and receipts 1953-1960 (Box-folder 14:1)
  - Accounts and receipts 1987-1988 (Box-folder 14:2)
  - Advertising, Programs 1955 (Box-folder 14:3)
  - Bank statements 1960-1961 (Box-folder 14:4)
  - Correspondence 1994-1996 (Box-folder 14:5)
  - Expense ledger 1953 (Box-folder 14:6)
  - Financial statements 1976-1977 (Box-folder 14:7)
  - Financial statements 1983 (Box-folder 14:8)
  - Financial statements 1987 (Box-folder 14:9)
  - Financial statements 1991-1992 (Box-folder 14:10)
  - Financial statements 1993 (Box-folder 14:11)
  - Financial statements 1994 (Box-folder 14:12)
  - Financial statements 1995 June-August (Box-folder 15:1)
  - Financial statements 1995 September-December (Box-folder 15:2)
  - Financial statements 1996 January-July (Box-folder 15:3)
  - Financial statements 1996 August-October (Box-folder 15:4)
  - Financial statements 1996 November-December (Box-folder 16:1)
  - Financial statements 1997 (Box-folder 16:2)
  - Financial statements 1999 (Box-folder 16:3)
  - Financial statements 2000 (Box-folder 16:4)
  - Fundraising campaigns 1996 (Box-folder 16:5)
  - Fundraising campaigns 1998 (Box-folder 16:6)
  - Fundraising campaigns 1999 (Box-folder 16:7)
  - Fundraising campaigns 2000-2001 (Box-folder 17:1)
  - Fundraising workshop 2000-2001 (Box-folder 17:2)
  - Grants 1996-1998 (Box-folder 17:2)
  - Kingsley, Sidney, Will bequeath 1988 (Box-folder 17:3)
  - Loans 1953-1967 (Box-folder 17:4)
  - Miscellaneous 1995 (Box-folder 17:5)
  - Virginia Commission for the Arts 1994-1996 (Box-folder 17:7)
  - Virginia Commission for the Arts 1996-1998 (Box-folder 17:8)
  - Virginia Foundation for the Humanities and Public Policy 1997 (Box-folder 17:9)
- Series V. Newspaper clippings and newsletters, 1953-2002., Extent: 3.5 cu. ft. (10 boxes). (Box 18-27)
  The Newspaper Clippings and Newsletters Series is housed in 10 boxes and arranged chronologically, with general materials to the front. Topics of the general newspaper clippings include, the early establishment of the Barksdale Theatre and the founding members; Muriel McAuley's modeling career; renovations of Hanover Tavern; anniversary celebrations for the Barksdale Theatre; biographies and stories on Muriel McAuley, Pete Kilgore, Nancy Kilgore, and Randy Strawderman; obituaries for several leading theatre members including Jay Lundy, Nancy Kilgore, and Muriel McAuley; the sale of Hanover Tavern; move of the Barksdale Theatre to Willow Lawn Shopping Center; stories relating to Richmond's other local theatres, Theatre Virginia, Theatre IV, and Swift Creek Mill Playhouse; lists of Richmond Times Dispatch yearly Phoebe Awards winners; and the hiring of artistic directors at the theatre.
  Following the general clippings are clippings relating to specific productions staged by Barksdale, 1953-2002. The clippings include reviews, audition notices, and photographs relating to the productions. The series also contains copies of theatre newsletters including, Curtain Up, Dramatists Quarterly, London Theatre News, National Theatre Critic's Reviews, New York Theatre Critic's Reviews, and Theatre Richmond. See also the Oversize series for oversize clippings.
  - Clippings, General 1953-1959 (Box-folder 18:1)
  - Clippings, General 1960-1969 (Box-folder 18:2)
  - Clippings, General 1973-1979 (Box-folder 18:3)
  - Clippings, General 1980 (Box-folder 18:4)
  - Clippings, General 1981 (Box-folder 18:5)
  - Clippings, General 1982 (Box-folder 18:6)
  - Clippings, General 1983 (Box-folder 19:1)
  - Clippings, General 1983 (Box-folder 19:2)
  - Clippings, General 1984 (Box-folder 19:3)
  - Clippings, General 1985 (Box-folder 19:4)
  - Clippings, General 1986 (Box-folder 19:5)
  - Clippings, General 1987 (Box-folder 19:6)
  - Clippings, General 1987 (Box-folder 19:7)
  - Clippings, General 1988 (Box-folder 19:8)
  - Clippings, General 1989 (Box-folder 19:9)
  - Clippings, General 1990 (Box-folder 19:10)
  - Clippings, General 1990 (Box-folder 19:11)
  - Clippings, General 1991 (Box-folder 19:12)
  - Clippings, General 1992 (Box-folder 19:13)
  - Clippings, General 1993 (Box-folder 19:14)
  - Clippings, General 1993 (Box-folder 19:15)
  - Clippings, General 1994 (Box-folder 19:16)
  - Clippings, General 1995 (Box-folder 19:15)
  - Clippings, General 1996 (Box-folder 20:1)
  - Clippings, General 1997 (Box-folder 20:2)
  - Clippings, General 1997 (Box-folder 20:3)
  - Clippings, General 1998 (Box-folder 20:4)
  - Clippings, General 1999 (Box-folder 20:5)
  - Clippings, General 2001-2001 (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Clippings, General n.d. (Box-folder 20:7)
  - Clippings, General n.d. (Box-folder 20:8)
  - Clippings, General n.d. (Box-folder 20:9)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Wavering Flame 1953 (Box-folder 21:1)
  - Clippings, Productions, Gold in the Hills 1954 (Box-folder 21:2)
  - Clippings, Productions, No Time for Comedy 1955 (Box-folder 21:3)
  - Clippings, Productions, Antigone 1955 (Box-folder 21:4)
  - Clippings, Productions, Hay Fever 1955 (Box-folder 21:5)
  - Clippings, Productions, Tons of Money 1955 (Box-folder 21:6)
  - Clippings, Productions, Ladies in Retirement 1956 (Box-folder 21:7)
  - Clippings, Productions, Biography 1956 (Box-folder 21:8)
  - Clippings, Productions, Present Laughter 1956 (Box-folder 21:9)
  - Clippings, Productions, Don Juan in Hell 1956 (Box-folder 21:10)
  - Clippings, Productions, Our Town 1956 (Box-folder 21:11)
  - Clippings, Productions, Bell, Book, and Candle 1956 (Box-folder 21:12)